Let's go back to our app now, and add a check box.
ここで 私たちのアプリに戻って チェックボックスを加えましょう
This will allow the user to select if they want the whipped cream topping on
これでユーザーはホイップクリームの トッピングを加えたいかどうか
their coffee.
選べます
It will look something like this, and then you can check this box.
このようになります そして このボックスをチェックすることができます
Go ahead and add a check box to the app now.
アプリにチェックボックスを 加えてみてください
This will allow the user to add a whipped cream topping
これによりユーザーはホイップクリームの トッピングを希望する場合に
on their drink if they want.
飲み物に追加できるようになります
When you click on this check box it should automatically animate to
このチェックボックスをクリックすると 自動的にこの状態へと
this state.
なるはずです
Also add a header that says toppings.
トッピングというヘッダーも加えましょう
There's only one topping now, but we're going to add another one later.
現在 トッピングはひとつだけですが 後でもうひとつ追加します
If you click on the order button, the order summary shows, and
オーダーボタンをクリックすると オーダーの要約が表示されます
it's still the same as before.
これは以前と同じままです
Eventually, we're going to modify it so
いずれは これが ホイップクリームのトッピングが
it shows whether you have the whipped cream topping or not.
あるかどうかを表示するように 修正します
For this next coding task, just focus on adding this check box and this header.
次のタスクですが チェックボックスと ヘッダーの追加に集中しましょう
You haven't added a check box to the layout before,
まだレイアウトにチェックボックスを 追加していませんが
but here's your chance to learn.
これが学ぶ機会です
You can look up online how to do this or you can check out
この方法はオンラインで探すか または Common Android Views の
the Common Android Views cheat sheet, which is linked in the instructor notes.
チートシートを見ることができます これは インストラクターノートにリンクされています
Whichever way you decide to figure it out,
どちらの手段で方法を学ぶ決定を するかにせよ
when your app launches it should look something like this.
アプリを実行すると このように なるはずです
Also note that I would like 24dp of space in between the box and
またボックスとホイップクリームという テキストの間には
the text whipped cream.
24dp のスペースが欲しい ということにも注意してください
Also use a font size of 16sp for the whipped cream text.
ホイップクリームのテキストには 16sp のフォントサイズを使用しましょう
By the way, when I draw out specific metrics like for spacing or
ところで スペーシングやフォントサイズ またはフォントの色に関する特定のメトリクスを
font sizes or font colors, that's actually called red lines.
引き出した場合 これは実際 レッドラインと呼ばれています
Red lines are very detailed specifications about how the visual
レッドラインはアプリの外観が どう見えるべきかに関する
appearance of the app should look like.
非常に詳細な仕様です
If you’re a developer working with a designer,
あなたがデザイナーと一緒に 仕事をしているデベロッパーなら
you’ll probably get a set of red lines for different screens in your app so
おそらくアプリ内の異なるスクリーンのための レッドラインを受け取ることでしょう
that you can build according to these specs.
これらの仕様に沿って開発が できるようにするためです
The red lines may include values for colors,size of views,
レッドラインには色 ビューのサイズ スペーシング フォントサイズや―
spacing, font sizes and font colors.
フォントの色に関する値を含む場合があります
These are the red lines for
これらは Android アプリ開発の
the sunshine app in the developing Android apps Udacity course.
Udacity コースにおける Sunshine アプリのためのレッドラインです
Keeping this in mind, go ahead and
これを覚えておいて
start planning how you're going to build out this layout.
このレイアウトをどう開発するか 計画し始めてみましょう
Remember the three steps that we taught you in lesson one for
レイアウトの開発に関して私たちが レッスン１で教えた３つのステップを
building any layout.
思い出してください
First, select the views that you need.
まずは 必要なビューを選択すること
Then position them, and then style them.
次に これらの位置を決定し スタイルを決定すること
In the text boxes provided, write down what you need to do in each step.
提示されたテキストボックスに 各ステップで 必要なことを書き出しましょう
Once you've planned it out, then go ahead and add this to your app.
計画が済んだら 先へ進んで これをあなたのアプリに追加してみましょう
Ironically, I don't have a check box for
あいにく このタスクを完了したときに
you to check when you're done with this task.
チェックできる チェックボックスは用意していません